翻译/时间轴：@尘世劫
校对/压制：@MarvelUniverse
打住
Don't.
啊？
What?
我都料到你想说什么了
I can just feel you about to say it.
反正你别说出来
Just don't say it.
我觉得我们不该冲动
I think we should bail.
小本，现在说这个已经太迟了
Benny, it's too late for that.
拜托，克莱尔，我们...
C'mon Claire, we..
我们压根儿不清楚自己在干什么
We don't know what we're dealing here
我清楚啊
I do.
不，你不清楚
No, you don't!
不，我清楚得很
Yes, I do!
我真的很清楚好么
I really do okay,
那玩意儿就这么从天而降
That thing fell out of the sky,
掉到我们怀里
into our laps.I mean,
我相信这就是一种暗示
to me that's a sign, okay?
你凭什么那么确定这东西会
What makes you so sure that
为我们指向一个正确的方向？
the sign is pointing in the right direction?
因为你啊
You make me sure.
是你启动了它
Cause you got it to work.
你总说我们值得拥有更好的未来，不是么？
Always said that we deserve better, right?
所以，我不想再苦苦等着别人给我们机会
So, i don't wanna wait for somebody to give us a chance.
是时候由我们自己创造自己的未来了
It's time that we took a chance for ourselves.
但愿你是对的
I hope you're right.
会的，我总都是对的
I am, I'm always right.
正如我选择对了你
I'm always right about you.
好吧
Okay.
加油
漫威影业 出品
漫威短片
47号物品
（快！全都趴下！）
(Go! Everybody down!)
（快离开这里！快点！）
(Get out! Go! Go!)
你现在看到的是宾夕法尼亚州的艾伦镇
What you're looking at is Allentown, Pennsylvania.
时间是纽约大战五天后
Five days after the Battle of New York.
（抱歉，你还好么）
(Sorry, are you okay?)
这是最糟糕的情况
This is a worst case scenario.
请告诉我为什么一件失灵的外星武器
Please tell me why is the one piece of Alien techie failed
突然间又可以用了
to capture is now functioning.
（快跑）
(Let's go.)
已经有四起类似事件的报告了
There are four confirmed reports of similar incidents.
弗吉尼亚州的里士满
Richmond, Virginia.
纽约大战七天后
Seven days after the Battle of New York,
又过了两天
Queensbury, North Carolina,
北卡罗来纳州的格林斯伯勒
Two days after that,
隔天下午是南卡罗来纳州的查尔斯顿
Charleston, South Carolina, the following afternoon.
（多有打扰）
(Excuse me.)
（小本！）
(Benny!)
（-小本！ -我得走了）
(-Benny! -I gota...)
而佐治亚州的帕萨迪纳
Pasadena, Georgia
（快跑快跑）
(Run! Run!)
就在昨天早上
yesterday morning.
我去过那里
I have been there.
那里街尾的猪肉卷特别好吃呢
They do a great pulled pork right down the street.
我怎么觉得你对这个任务一点儿也不严肃
I don't think you're taking this assignment very seriously.
真巧，我也刚想这么说你呢
That's funny, I was just thinking the same thing about you.
在你收集那些监控录像的时候
While you've been in here gathering video clips
我已经在外面调查好了
I've been out investigating.
发现在基维斯特岛刚卖出一艘28英尺的皮尔森游艇
It turns out a used 28 foot Pearson was taken off the marker in Key West.
根据卖家交代
Spoke to the former owner,
是被一对夫妇用现金买走了
a couple matching our description paid in cash.
游艇刚驶出不到24小时
Boat gets out of Dry Dock in 24 hours.
所以
So...
我认为该采取行动了
I'd like to get a move on.
我明白，因为科尔森探员
I understand, Agent Coulson.
抱歉，老毛病
I'm sorry, force of habit.
我们都怀念他
We all miss him.
西特韦尔探员，给你的任务
Your orders, Agent Sitwell.
缴回武器
Retrieve the weapons tech,
干掉那两个...
and neutralise ...
不法之徒
the two outlaws.
南福罗里达州
这武器快把我的手腕废了
Thing's a killer on the wrist.
就像得了...
Feels i'm getting advanced...
腕管综合症什么的
carpal tunnel or something
怎么了
What?
我们成功了
We did it.
多少钱？
How much?
够多了
Enough.
多到什么程度？
Enough enough?
多到够我们逍遥自在了
Enough to do whatever we want.
从现在到永远
Now and forever.
隔壁在搞什么鬼？
What the hell is that?
额，我喜欢这首歌
Oh, i like that song.
你能不能...
Can you please...
好的，没问题，我这就去说几句
Yup, okay.. okay, i'll say something.
你就这么躺着，不要动，我马上回来
Just stay right there, don't move, I'll be right back
有人么？
Hello?
不要再挣扎了
Please stop squirming.
班杰明，如果你不再挣扎就会舒...
Banjamin this would go a lot smoother if...
克莱尔，有警察！
Claire, it's the cops!
快卧倒！宝贝儿
Hit the deck, baby.
呀，我的手腕
Ay, my wrist...
小本！
Benny!
小本你还好么？
Benny are you okay?
克莱尔
Claire.
你得让它多冷却一会儿
You should go a lot cooler!
小本？
Benny?
或许我们还能...
Maybe we can do...
还想冒险？
Risky?
或许还能...
something...
你知道我们刚才在哪个位置么？
Did you even know where we were?
当然知道
I do...
你确定？
You knew?
我知道我在做什么
I knew what I was doing.
听着，我们会被抓去关了
Listen, we're gonna get arrested.
好吧，嘘，嘘
Okay, shh shh
嗨，嗨...刚才的事非常抱歉
Hi, hi.. I'm so sorry about before.
希望我没有...伤到你
I hope i didn't hurt you..?
曼哈顿上空的传送门关闭之后
47 known alien objects hit the ground
有47件外星武器从天而降
after the portal closed above Manhattan.
全都失灵
All dormant,
全都坏了
all dead.
除了这个
Execpt this one.
只有这个还能用
This one works just fine.
知道为什么不？
Any idea why that is?
是小本启动的
Benny got it to work.
看什么？就是你啊
What? You did.
好吧我可以启动给你看
Well i can show you how to do it.
对啊，演示给他看
Show him, show him up.
对对对
Yeah, yeah.
他真的真的..
He can show you really really...
绝不骗你
Totally.
是的
Yeah.
他很乐意演示给你看
He would love to show you.
怎么样都行，就是别...别抓我们入狱
Just anything, but we can't...we can't go to jail.
看看他，他挨不了监狱的
Look at him, he can't go to jail.
谁说要让你们进监狱了
Who said anything about jail?
我的任务是缴回武器
I was sent here to retrieve the weapon,
然后把你们清理掉
and to neutralise you.
（西特韦尔验证请求）
（通过验证）
你特么死哪儿去了
Where the hell have you been?
10个小时之前就该报告了
Report was due 10 hours ago.
汽车旅馆要求赔偿损失42000美元
42,000$ worth a damage at the motel,
你知不知道弗瑞局长都快追到我头上...
you know I've gotten fury breathing down my neck..
嗨
Hi.
布莱克探员，向你介绍一下克莱尔・维斯
Agent Blake, I'd like you to meet Claire Wise
还有本杰明波・洛克
and Benjamin Pollack.
本杰明是神盾局研发智库的新成员
Benjamin here is the latest addition to the SHIELD R&D think tank.
他将运用反向工程帮我们分析外星武器
He's gonna help us reverse engineer some of the alien tech.
准备好加入我们了么？
You ready to get that badge?
当然
Yes.
那啥，西特韦尔你等等
Aaah, hold on a second Sitwell.
噢我忘记说了
Oh, I forgot to mention.
克莱尔是你的新助理
Claire is your new assistant.
什么鬼？
What?
准确的说，是女学员
I mean, protegee.
噢，简直太荒谬了
Ya, that's ridiculous.
你应该把你毕生所学的知识和技能
Impart upon her all the knowledge and skills
都一五一十地教给她
that have made you the man you are today
好吧，可是这里没有多余的座位了
Well, we don't even have another chair here.
噢，那才荒谬呢
Now, that's ridiculous.
西特韦尔！
Sitwell!
（我先走啦，宝贝）
(I gona go, baby.)
西特韦尔！
Sitwell!
嗨
Hey.
请问你会泡咖啡么？
Do you know how to make coffee?
不会
No.
导演
编剧
制片人
出品人
联合制片人
丽兹・卡潘
（克莱尔扮演者）
杰西・布拉德福德
（本杰明扮演者）
麦克斯米利安诺・贺南德兹
（西特韦尔特工扮演者）
提图斯・维里沃
（布莱克特工扮演者）
摄影导演
视觉特效
音乐
剪辑
艺术指导
选角导演
服装设计
音效
翻译/时间轴：@尘世劫
校对/压制：@MarvelUniverse
漫威影业